Victoria Onishchuk

Product Designer, UX, UI, Mobile, VR

E-mail: victoria.onishchuk@gmail.com

Portfolio: http://victoriaonishchuk.com

Prototypes: https://goo.gl/tl2GB7

I work for redesigning our World in a little bit comfortable place for everyone and inspire others to do the same.

I can \neq : develop a product strategy and design concept; Take full ownership of projects; Translate product requirements into user flows; Create User Personas, Scenarios and Journeys; Build low and high fidelity prototypes; Support the UX research, tests and analysed the results; Design interactions and visual design; Build a component based design system; Prepare assets for build and development; Work for multiple platforms and devices: iOS, Android, Phone, Tablet; Collaborate with designers, product owners, developers, researchers; Use Sketch, Adobe CC, Lucidchart, Axure, Pinto, Framer, Zepplin, HTML, CSS, JS.

Education

British Higher School of Art and Design: Interaction design (2008-2009), Type and typography (2011-2013), Design in media (2013-2014).

Master's Degree, Computer Science Odessa State Polytechnic University (2001-2006)

Languages: English (fluent), German (basic)



Experience

Product UX designer at

Archilogic,

Tadaweb,

Factod

(from 11.2016)

Early stage startups consulting: **Researching**, interviewing users and collecting data; Rebuilding informational architecture and user flows; Rethinking complex, innovative and unusual interfaces; Finding the priority and systemising ideas and features into lean development.

Product mobile designer at **Art. Lebedev Studio** (11.2014–10.2016)

Successfully designed 8 great products inside different teams; Implemented the culture of UX in mobile design development; Promoted the informational architecture like a part of a design process and MindMapping like an instrument for UX teams; Popularised new technologies like VR/AR and created the first project in Studio with it; Developed and provided first user testing scheme adapted for agencies. Then passed this knowledge to other teams; Started the good tradition of every week design checkup; Provided mentorship and inspired colleagues to grow up the right way; Tried to rethink and change the management system. Failed...

Lead Interactive designer and owner at **LaborUnion** (06.2012-09.2014)

Started a small agency business targeting the digital market and startups consulting: **OnMusicStage** (Social music network for young musicians); **KamaGames Studio** (Social dating network "Friends"); **Ruvents** (platform for organising conference and events)

Senior UX/UI designer at Jeltofiol-Design Studio (09.2011-05.2012) UX/UI designer at Bigateam, Media Agency (09.2008-07.2011)

